Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. William Woodville Rockhill papers (MS Am 2121): Guide.
William Woodville Rockhill papers,
- I. Correspondence and other papers
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to John J. A. MacMurray; [n.p.] 6 Nov 1911., (2147); 3l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(W. W. Rockhill) to Philander C. Knox; [n.p.] 8 Dec 1911., (2148); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Prof. Bunzaburo Natsumoto; New York 13 Jan 1912., (2149); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of L.s.(W. W. Rockhill) to Thomas J. O'Brien; [n.p.] 29 May 1912., (2150); 4l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of L.(unsigned) to Philander C. Knox; Constantinople, 30 May 1912., (2151); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(W. W. R.) to "My dear Colleague"; [Constantinople] 29 Jun 1912., (2152); 4l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of L.s.(W. W. Rockhill) to [George Ernest] Morrison; Constantinople, 2 Jun 1912., (2153); 4l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Philander Chase Knox; Constantinople 23 Oct 1912., (2154); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(W. W. R.) to Robert Woods Bliss; [Constantinople] 26 Oct 1912., (2155); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unfinished) to Charles J. Arnell; [Constantinople] 11 Nov 1912., (2156); 2l.
    Enclosed: Typescript (c.c.) of "Arrangement of Volume". 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Woodrow Wilson; [Constantinople] 18 Dec 1912., (2157); 3l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Wahid Bey; [n.p.] 17 [?] 1913., (2158); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Charles Jonathan Arnell; [Constantinople] 12 Feb 1913., (2159); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to George F. Fleming; [Constantinople] 19 Feb 1913., (2160); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to "President of the Connecticut Branch of the Society of the Colonial Dames of America"; Constantinople, 27 Mar 1913., (2161); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Lincoln Safe Deposit Co.; [Constantinople] 24 Feb 1913., (2162); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to [?]; [Constantinople] 1 Mar 1913., (2163); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Yuan Shih-k'ai; [Constantinople] 18 Mar 1913., (2164); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Caspar Whitney; [Constantinople] 27 Mar 1913., (2165); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to George E. Fleming; [Constantinople] 23 Mar 1913., (2166); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to J.C. O'Laughlin; [Constantinople] 14 Apr 1913., (2167); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to R. V. Oulahan; 14 Apr 1913., (2167a); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of L.(unsigned) to Robert H. Patchin; [Constantinople] 14 Apr 1913., (2168); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Professor Kentok Hori; [Constantinople] 28 Apr 1913., (2169); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Peter Augustus Jay; [Constantinople] 28 Apr 1913., (2170); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to W. W. Oswald; [Constantinople] 29 Apr 1913., (2171); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to John Van A. MacMurray; [Constantinople] 11 Apr 1913., (2172); 6l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to J. O. P.; [Constantinople] 16 Apr 1913., (2173); 2l.
    Enclosed: Typescript (c.c.) of Corrections to be made in book. 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Nelson T. Johnson; [n.p.] 28 Apr 1913., (2174); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Lincoln Safe Deposit Co.; [Constantinople] 2 May 1913., (2175); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to William J. Bryan; Constantinople, 3 May 1913., (2176); 3l.
    Not located at time of end-processing in August of 2003.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Moore; Constantinople, 3 May 1913., (2177); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Messrs. McBride, Nast Co.; [Constantinople] 7 May 1913., (2178); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Gh'en Kuo-ch 'Uan; [Constantinople] 16 May 1913., (2179); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to "The Asiatic Quarterly Review"; [Constantinople] 16 May 1913., (2180); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Herbert Putnam; [Constantinople] 17 May 1913., (2181); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of L.(unsigned) to Andrew Carnegie; Constantinople, 30 May 1913., (2182); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Transcript of Telegram s.(Rockhill) to "Mrs. Hoppin"; [Constantinople] 6 Jun [1913], (2183); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to [?]; [Constantinople] 7 Jun 1913., (2184); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Kentok Hori; [Constantinople] 16 Jun 1913., (2185); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Jesse Williamson; [Constantinople] 19 Jun 1913., (2186); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Charles D. Jameson; [Constantinople] 20 Jun 1913., (2187); 3l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Frederick Mc Cormick; [Constantinople] 26 June 1913., (2188); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to President Wheeler; [Constantinople] 31 Oct 1913., (2189); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Gilbert H. Grosvenor; [Constantinople] 7 Nov 1913., (2190); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Transcript of L.[William Woodville Rockhill] to president Yuan; [n.p., 1914], (2190a); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to S. R. Berton; Peking, 12 Feb 1914., (2191); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(W. W. Rockhill) to Admiral TsaiTing-kan; [Peking] 14 Feb 1914., (2192); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of L.(unsigned) to John Hays Hammond; Peking, 20 Feb 1914., (2193); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) to L.(unsigned) to Chou Tzu-chi; [Peking] 2 Mar 1914., (2194); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(W. W. R.) to Tsai Ting-kan; [Peking] 8 Mar 1914., (2195); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of "Suggestions" to Admiral Tsai Ting-kan; [n.p.] 11 Mar 1914., (2196); 3l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of L.s.(c.c.)(W. W. R.) to Admiral Tsai [Ting-kan]; [Peking] 14 Mar 1914., (2197); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-19141 A. Receipt .s.(W. W. Rockhill) to [Admiral Tsai Ting-kan]; Peking, 23 Mar 1914., (2198); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Admiral Tsai [Ting-kan]; Hankow, 6 Apr 1914., (2199); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to "Mr. Reinsch;" Shanghai, 6 May 1914., (2200); 4l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.([W.W.Rockhill) to Admiral Ts'ai; Shanghai, 7 May 1914., (2200a); 3l.
    Enclosure: Typescript of L.(unsigned) to "Your Excellency"; Shanghai, 7 May 1914. 3l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(W. W. Rockhill) to Admiral Ts'ai [Ting-kan]; Litchfield, 10 Jun 1914., (2201); 5l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Dhen Chin-tao; Litchfield, 12 Jun 1914., (2202); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typed L.s.(W. W. Rockhill) to Admiral Ts'ai [Ting-kan]; Litchfield, 23 Jun 1914., (2203); 6l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript L.s.(W. W. R.) to K. F. Shah; Litchfield, 24 Jun 1914], (2204); 1l.
    Enclosure: Typescript (c.c.) of Memorahdum; [Litchfield, 24 Jun 1914] 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(W. W. R.) to Patrick Gallagher; [Litchfield] 27 Jun 1914., (2205); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(W. W. R.) to Admiral Ts'ai [Ting-kan]; Litchfield, 29 Jun 1914., (2206); 4l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to "Mr. McCormick"; [n.p., 3 Jul 1914], (2207); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(W. W. R.) to "Mr. Chen"[i.e. Chen Chin tao]; [n.p.] 5 Jul 1914., (2208); 4l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsighed) to Admiral Ts'ai [Ting-kan]; [Litchfield] 10 Jul 1914., (2209); 5l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(W. W. Rockhill) to Admiral Ts'ai [Ting-kan]; Litchfield, 31 Jul 1914., (2210); 4l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to [John Otway Percy] Bland; [Litchfield] 4 Aug 1914., (2211); 6l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(W.W.R.) to Chen Chin Tao; [n.p.] 12 Aug 1914., (2211a); 6l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Admiral Ts'ai [Ting-kan]; [Litchfield] 14 Aug 1914., (2212); 4l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of L.s.(W. W. Rockhill) to [Berthold] Laufer; Litchfield, 8 Sep 1914., (2213); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(W. W. R) to Admiral Ts'ai [Ting-kan]; [Litchfield] 9 Sep 1914., (2214); 7l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of L.s.(W. W. Rockhill) to [Berthold] Laufer; Litchfield, 16 Sep 1914., (2215); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(W. W. R.) to Admiral Ts'ai [Ting-kan]; Litchfield, 22 Sep 1914., (2216); 8l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Admiral Ts'ai [Ting-kan]; Litchfield, 5 Oct 1914., (2217); 4l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of L.s.(W. W. Rockhill) to [Berthold] Laufer; Litchfield, 7 Oct 1914., (2218); 2l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of L.(unsigned) to Admiral Ts'ai [Ting-kan]; Litchfield, 21 Oct 1914., (2219); 5l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of L.(c.c.)s. (The American Group) to "Secretary of State"; [Litchfield, 6 Nov 1914], (2220); 5l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of L.s.(W. W. Rockhill) to [Berthold] Laufer; Litchfield, 7 Nov 1914., (2221); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Ms.L.(unsigned) to K. T. Shah; Litchfield, 17 Nov 1914., (2222); 5l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typed L.s.(W. W. Rockhill) to [Berthold] Laufer; Litchfield, 14 Nov 1914., (2223); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(W. W. R.) to Admiral Ts'ai [Ting-kan]; Litchfield, 18 Nov 1914., (2224); 3l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Memoranda; [n.p., n.d.] [3]l., (2225)
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Memorandum in re treaty of Peking of 1869 etc. [n.p., n.d.], (2226); [6]p.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Memorandum in re The Ning-po sea-going junks; [n.p., n.d.], (2227); [1]p.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Notes on Mootang; [n.p., 188-?], (2228); 8p.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Memoranda in re Lamas, etc.; [n.p., 188-?] [3]l., (2229)
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Maps; [n.p., 188-?] [3]l., (2230)
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Printed map of Mongolia etc. with autograph annotations; [n.p., 189-?], (2231); [1]p.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typed Memorandum in re diplomatic representation; [n.p., 1894], (2232); [2]p.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Memorandum in re "Concessions for R. R. granted Japan in Manchuria"; [Peking, 1914], (2233); [2]p.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of article "The Question of outer Mongolia" S.(W. W. R.); Peking, 15 Feb 1914., (2234); 25l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of Speech at annual dinner of The American University club of Shanghai; [Shanghai] 8 May 1914., (2235); 2l.
    [remaining leaves wanting]
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Memorandum in re Chinese officials, etc.; [Peking] 11 May 1914., (2236); [3]p.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typed article with ms. emendations in re impact of the West on China s.(W. W. Rockhill); [n.p.,] 23 Jul 1914., (2237); [3]p.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of Article in re present condition in China, s.(W. W. Woodville Rockhill); [n.p.] 5 Nov 1914., (2238); 37l.
    With autograph annotation "written for the Journal of the Central Asian Society, London".
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of speech at dinner of Asiatic Institute; New York, 12 Nov 1914., (2239); 20l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typed List of "Writings of W. W. Rockhill"; [n.p.] 1883-1912., (2240); 3l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Certificate of Marriage s.(John Hutchins); Litchfield, 25 Apr 1900., (2241); 1l.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typed List of "Memberships in the Following Societies"; [n.p.] 1880-1909. With autograph annotations., (2242)
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Typescript of "Governmental Services of William Woodville Rockhill"; [n.p., n.d.], (2243); 1l.
  - Rodgers, Alexander A.L.s. (Alex. Rodgers) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; San Francisco, 11 Feb [18]96., (2243a); ([4]p.)
  - Rodgers, Alexander. A.L.s.(Alex. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 1 Aug 1899., (2244); ([5]p.)
  - Rodgers, Alexander. A.L.s.(Alex. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 22 Aug 1899., (2245); ([6]p.)
  - Rodgers, Alexander. A.L.s.(Alex. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 25 Aug 1899., (2246); ([3]p.)
  - Rodgers, Alexander. A.L.s.(Alex. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 7 Sep 1899., (2247); ([3]p.)
  - Rodgers, J. S. A.L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 15 Aug 1905., (2248); 3l.
  - Rodgers, J. S. A.L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 1 Sep 1905., (2249); 6l.
  - Rodgers, J. S. A.L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 11 Sep 1905., (2250); ([7]p.)
    Enclosed: A.L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 11 Sep 1905. ([3]p.)
  - Rodgers, J. S. A.L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 27 Dec [19]05., (2251); ([3]p.)
  - Rodgers, J. S. A.L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 29 Dec 1905., (2252); ([3]p.)
  - Rodgers, J. S. Typed L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to W[illiam] W[oodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 18 Jan 1906., (2253); 7l.
  - Rodgers, J. S. A.L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 22 Jan [19]07., (2254); ([3]p.)
  - Rodgers, J. S. A.L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Shanghai] 31 Jan 1906., (2255); ([5]p.)
  - Rodgers, J. S. A.L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Shanghai] 6 Feb 1906., (2256); ([1]p.)
  - Rodgers, J. S. Typed L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 13 Apr 1906., (2257); 2l.
  - Rodgers, J. S. A.L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Shanghai] 14 May 1906., (2258); ([3]p.)
  - Rodgers, J. S. A.L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Shanghai] 29 Jun 1906., (2259); ([3]p.)
  - Rodgers, J. S. A.L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Shanghai] 21 Jul 1906., (2260); ([5]p.)
  - Rodgers, J. S. A.L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Shanghai,] 6 Feb [19]07., (2261); ([5]p.)
  - Rodgers, J. S. Typed L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 21 Dec 1906., (2262); 4l.
  - Rodgers, J. S. A.L.s.(J. S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 23 Feb [19]07., (2263); [3]p.
  - Rodgers, J. S. A.L.s.(J.S. Rodgers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 22 Apr [1907], (2264); ([4]p.)
  - Rodriquez, Jose Ignacio, 1831-1907. Typed L.s.(Jose Igno. Rodriguez) to W[illiam] W[oodville] Rockhill; Washington, 12 Jan 1906., (2265); 5l.
  - Romero, Matias, 1837-1898. A.L.s.(M. Romero) to William W[oodville] Rockhill; Cape May, 12 Aug 1896., (2266); ([1]p.)
  - Romero, Matias, 1837-1898. Typed L.s.(M. Romero) to W[illiam] W[oodville] Rockhill; Washington, 27 Mar 1897., (2267); 1l.
  - Roosa, F. P. Typed L.s.(F. P. Roosa) to W[illiam]W[oodville] Rockhill; New York, 23 Nov 1911., (2268); 2l.
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S.,1858-1919. Typed L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to W[illiam Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 25 Sep 1895., (2269); 2l.
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1858-1919. A.L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to [?]; [New York] 12 Feb [18]96., (2270); ([3]p.)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1858-1919. Typed L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to W[illiam] W[oodville] Rockhill; New York, 17 Feb 1896., (2271); 1l.
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1858-1919. Typed L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to Cha[rle]s [Laurie McCawley]; Albany, 9 Mar 1899., (2272); 1l.
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1858-1919. Typed L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Oyseer Bay, 21 Jul 1900., (2273); 1l.
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1858-1919. Typed L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 18 May 1905., (2274); 2l.
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1858-1919. Typed L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to William [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 31 May 1905., (2275); ([1]p.)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1858-1919. Typed L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Oyster Bay, 9 Aug 1905., (2276); ([1]p.)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1858-1919. Typed L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Oyster Bay, 22 Aug 1905., (2277); ([2]p.)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1858-1919. Typed L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Oyster Bay, 29 Aug 1905., (2278); ([2]p.)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1858-1919. Typed L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 20 Feb 1906., (2279); ([1]p.)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1859-1919. Typed L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 14 Jul 1906., (2280); ([1]p.)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1859-1919. Typed L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 6 Aug 1906., (2281); ([2]p.)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1859-1919. Typed L.a.(Wm. Loeb, Jr. Secretary) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 5 Nov 1906., (2282); ([1]p.)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1859-1919. Typed L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 17 Dec 1908., (2283); ([2]p.)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1858-1919. A.L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; Sagamor Hill, 15 Jan [1915], (2284); ([2]p.)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1887-1944. A.L.s.(Theodore Roosevelt) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 16 Sep [1913]., (2285); 1l.
  - Root, Elihu, 1845-1937. Typed L.s.(Elihu Root) to William [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 13 Apr 1908., (2286); ([2]p.)
  - Root, Elihu, 1845-1937. Transfript of Telegram s.(Elihu Root) to F. D. Cheshire; Washington, 10 Nov 1905., (2287); 1l.
  - Rosenberg, F. A.L.s.(F. Rosenberg) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; St. Petersburg, 11/24 Nov 1911., (2288); ([3]p.)
  - Ross, Sir Edward Denison, 1871-1940. A.L.s.(E. Denison Ross) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Darjeeling, 18 May 1910., (2289); ([4]p.)
  - Ross, Sir Edward Denison, 1871-1940. A.L.s.(E. Denison Ross) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Darjeeling, 5 Oct 1910., (2290); ([4]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p., 188-?], (2291); ([1]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 30 Oct [188-?], (2292); ([1]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 9 Aug 1882., (2293); ([1]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A. Postcard s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Deal, 31 Aug [1882]., (2294); [1]p.
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A. Postcard s.(R. R.) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 17 Sep [1882]., (2295); [1]p.
    Address on p. [2]
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1892. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 27 Sep [1882]., (2296); ([1]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1892. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 11 Oct 1882., (2297); ([2]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1892. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 11 Jan 1883., (2298); ([1]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 6 Apr [1883]., (2299); ([1]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 5 Sep 1884., (2300); ([3]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. signature torn away) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 10 Oct [1884]., (2301); 1l.
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 5 Mar 1886., (2302); ([2]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 30 Jul 1886., (2303); ([3]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 5 Nov 1886., (2304); 1l.
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 3 Dec 1886., (2305); ([3]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 11 Feb 1887., (2306); ([2]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 25 Mar 1887. ([2]p, (2307)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 15 Jul 1887., (2308); ([2]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 11 Nov 1887., (2309); ([3]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 20 Jan 1888., (2310); ([2]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1892. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 12 Sep [1888]., (2311); ([2]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 30 Nov [1889]., (2312); ([1]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 4 Dec 1889., (2313); ([2]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R. Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 20 Mar 1891., (2314); ([3]p.)
  - Rost, Reinhold, 1822-1896. A.L.s.(R.Rost) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 23 May [1891]., (2314a); ([3]p.)